expatfinder.com 2017-06-06

# 

  * Home

**Privacy Policy**

Last updated 08 October 2015.

The founders and employees of ExpatFinder take your privacy very seriously. Regardless of the purpose for which it is submitted, it is Interexpat Pte Ltd's policy to maintain all Personal Information as confidential. Your privacy is our top concern.

The Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the ExpatFinder.com site, and when you use our services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use by ExpatFinder**

We collect personally identifiable information when you visit ExpatFinder pages, when you register your contact details, when you complete certain forms on our website, when you enter information to receive email newsletters, other offers and promotions or when you choose to contact us for any reason.

We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, ExpatFinder cookie information and the page you requested. We use information for three general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

Third party information: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You can opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie (DoubleClick cookie) enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie (DoubleClick cookie) for interest-based advertising by visiting the [Ad settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**Information Sharing and Disclosure by ExpatFinder**

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

We have your consent to share the information;   
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of us to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);   
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or   
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the ExpatFinder Terms of Use, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a notice on this site. You agree that such posting will constitute sufficient and adequate notice to you of the changes. You agree that your continued use of our products or services after such amendment will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the modified policy.

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions email us at [contact@expatfinder.com](mailto:contact@expatfinder.com)

### Purchase your relocation   
City Guide Now

### International School Fee Survey 2016   

##### As seen on:
